[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 9]
Your Highness.
Are you trying to elope?
Isn't this Lord Ning of the Yulin Guard?
Don't come any closer,
or I'll kill her!
Ning Changyue.
Cut the crap.
Lord Ning, are you trying to hold the princess hostage?
Since you've caught us,
and I can't take her away alive,
then we'll die together!
Ning Changyue! Ning Changyue!
Let me go!
What a tragic drama of star-crossed lovers.
In the past,
if I were in a good mood,
I might have let you two go off together.
But now,
what a pity.
You, a princess out of favor,
have caught the eye of General Yu.
So today,
I have no choice but to be the bad guy
who breaks you two
apart.
Princess Ningjia, receive the edict.
By the grace of Heaven,
the Emperor decrees:
Princess Ningjia is gentle and intelligent.
General Yu is unparalleled in loyalty and bravery.
They are a perfect match.
I hereby grant them marriage,
to be wed on the auspicious day, the eighth day of the third lunar month,
to show my special favor.
Respect this.
I won't marry him. I won't marry him.
Let me go!
I won't marry him!
Song Yiqiu!
Let me go!
Your Highness, it seems you
have been led astray by some scum.
Your Highness.
Now you know
♪ Fate is hard to write, with karma left incomplete ♪
what you should do, right?
♪ Past lives burn away at dusk, old memories fade cold ♪
♪ Across lifetimes, my longing remains, leaving no regret ♪
♪ 3,000 years cannot undo the bitterness of one endless cycle ♪
♪ Watching time flow ♪
♪ Hearing the years sigh softly ♪
♪ Immortality still cannot bring fulfillment ♪
♪ Let fate tear everything apart ♪
♪ Our bond exists only because ♪
♪ I don't want to leave regrets behind ♪
♪ I'd forsake immortality to share your joys and sorrows ♪
♪ Don't ask how absurd the ending may be ♪
♪ I only want to use this lifetime ♪
♪ To trade it for eternity ♪
♪ Could we find our happy ending? ♪
A lowly wretch dares to covet royalty.
Go back to where you came from.
Take this sinner
to test the medicine.
What are you yelling about?
Shut up.
Stop yelling.
Stop crying.
I'm talking to him, not you.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
No more crying.
Stop shouting. Stop shouting.
Hurry.
Move.
Why are you just standing there?
Hurry up.
Legend has it
the Tree Spirit's inner core can bring the dead back to life,
restore flesh to bones, and grant immortality.
Hand over the inner core,
and you won't have to suffer like this.
How dare you ignore me.
Drain her blood.
-Yes. -Yes.
Song Yiqiu.
Run.
Come on.
Today is Princess Ningjia's wedding day.
This is a gift from the higher-ups.
Drink up,
and share the joy.
Come on.
Isn't this
Lord Ning, who was beaten half to death?
Lord Ning,
do you want some wedding wine?
Come on.
Fill it up for me again.
A toad dares to dream of a swan.
I haven't felt this good in a long time.
The woman you love is marrying someone else.
Why aren't you crying?
Come on, guys.
-Let's drink. -Okay.
Come here.
Bottoms up.
I don't deserve her.
I never did.
She is the moon in the sky,
and I am the mud on the ground.
Let's get drunk, bro.
Go get a pot of hot tea for the Princess.
Your Highness, it's me.
Xiaoyuan.
Your Highness,
there's no time.
I'll take you out of the palace according to Lord Ning's backup plan.
Xiaoyuan,
if they find out
you let me go, you'll be beheaded.
Lord Ning helped me.
His wish is to help you escape the palace.
I will also escape during the chaos.
Take this identity token
and go out through the west corner gate.
Lord Ning has arranged everything.
The carriage, travel documents, and route
are all at the usual place.
Your Highness,
I calculated the time before I came
and left a pile of firewood at the east corner gate.
Taking advantage of the chaos caused by the fire,
no one will recognize you.
Your Highness, go quickly.
No, I can't.
Your Highness,
the world is vast once you escape.
I hope your wishes come true.
Song Yiqiu,
you must escape.
The world outside is vast.
I hope
your wishes come true.
Come on.
There's a fire!
Fire!
Somebody help! There's a fire!
Look over there!
There really is a fire.
Fire!
Really!
Let me out!
Go!
Help! Hurry!
Don't just stand there. Run!
Run!
Hurry up!
Somebody!
Help!
Somebody help!
The fire is so big.
She'll definitely escape in the chaos.
Do you know where the prison is?
Your Highness, you can't go.
That's a dead end.
This is also the freedom I want.
Song Yiqiu.
Let us out!
Go! Hurry!
Run!
Over there!
Let us out!
Help me! Help me!
Please help me!
Help!
The door is open! Hurry!
Run!
Help us!
Let us out!
Hurry! Hurry!
Song Yiqiu.
Why are you here?
Go.
Don't worry about me.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Let's go!
Hurry.
I can't walk.
You can't leave if you take me.
No, no.
Leave me alone and go.
No.
Song Yiqiu.
You could have escaped in the chaos.
Why did you come back?
Our lives have been tied together
since you taught me how to draw a bow.
If we live, we live together.
If we die, we die together.
This is...
Their bond
actually generated a spiritual pill.
Eat it.
Maybe you can get a chance
to be together forever.
Pass on my decree:
The traitors Ningjia and Ning Changyue
released the Tree Spirit.
Kill them without mercy!
Stop!
After them!
Over there!
Watch out!
Hurry! Hyah!
That's a cliff. They can't escape now.
Let's go! Hurry!
Your Highness,
this is a dead end.
You have nowhere to run.
Are you afraid?
As long as I'm by your side,
I have nothing left to wish for.
Song Yiqiu,
from this day forward,
from the heavens above to the depths below,
may it always be you and me,
never to part.
We
will never part.